I brought you this hay from my shed.
Celina should be fine now.
Thank you! It's wonderful!
An oracle, huh?
It appears I am in your debt now,
my good friend, Myrale.
The Knight Girl
I haven't used my astral form
in eons. I'm a little nervous.
My. I knew I felt a familiar presence.
It's been too long, my old dragon friend.
It has, Goddess Myrale.
"Goddess"? Somebody's been dyed
in the ways of the earth.
Myrale, please don't tease me so.
On that note...
I know. This is about the lamia, isn't it?
Yes. I appreciate it.
There's no telling what would've
happened without your oracle.
It take it things worked out, then?
Thanks to you, yes. You have my gratitude.
I'm impressed that you realized
it was me, reborn as a human.
I felt your soul among the
prayers offered to me.
And it sparkled with the joy of life.
It surprised me because you
used to be so sick of living.
I can't deny it.
When the hero's blade pierced my heart,
I felt no despair over dying.
Only a blank realization
that this was the end.
But my rebirth as a human changed that.
I realized that the people on the surface
live each day like it's their last.
Their lives, as fleeting as they
may seem to celestial beings,
burn extremely bright.
You're shining quite brightly yourself.
Lately, I've come to sense the
pure joy in your heart and soul.
Well...
It's the same for the lamia.
I see. Thank you.
Dolan!
Wake up! The day has come!
Please knock before you come in.
S-Sorry. Let me start over.
It's fine.
What's up? You seem happy.
Well, I had a dream where an old
friend said some kind words to me.
Anyway, what's this about today?
How could you? We promised to plant
potatoes with Christina today.
It'd make her so sad if
she found out you forgot.
Oh, yes, that was the plan.
Extra, extra! Get the latest on
the case of the missing women!
So it's you. I'll open the door right away.
You have mail, Headmistress.
Thank you, as always.
You may place them there.
Thank you, too.
Please read it at once.
Today's mail is special.
Oh? Could it be...
It's from Christina!
It seems like you're eager
to have me read it at once.
C-Can you blame me? It's from
Christina, the pride of our academy!
Fair. I'll read it right away.
"Dear Headmistress Olivia, I trust
this letter finds you in fine health.
Some time has passed since..."
Some time has passed since my
stay in Verun Village began.
Lying further north than Galoa, Verun faces
harsh climes and threats to its safety.
As such, combat training is a
fixture for the villagers.
I haven't seen the vice captain
on the back foot in ages.
Come on, you know she ain't serious yet.
Sheesh, these people love
to run their mouth.
But he's not wrong.
You aren't serious yet.
Very well. I'll start taking this seriously.
But know that I won't be able to hold back.
Just the way I like it!
Your skill with the sword is extraordinary.
I've lost, and handily.
Please. Your sword was swift,
sharp, and beautiful to boot.
I couldn't take my eyes off it.
A marvelous mock battle, Christina.
Christina, we're all about
to have lunch together.
Would you like to join us?
Show Christina Verun's brand
of hospitality, you guys!
While the conditions here are harsh,
its people are warm, and they have
readily made me a part of their lives.
Please eat all you like.
Thank you.
Have some of this, too. I don't
know if you'll like it, though.
All the food in this village is
delicious, so I'll gladly have some.
Is something the matter?
Oh, my apologies!
It's just... you're so pretty.
Care to join us for a drink, Christina?
Er...
In my opinion, you should decline.
The captain doesn't know when to stop.
You'll be drinking till morning.
Not true!
Captain Balan, don't try to drag
Christina into your nonsense.
Show some respect.
Huh? I don't particularly...
R-Right. I apologize if I offended you.
I guess...
I'll make do with you guys tonight.
Stop trying to run.
Have a good night, then.
Dolan, is that...
Yeah, looks like it.
So it is Christina!
Training with the sword?
Y-Yes.
Huh? Is something the matter?
No, I...
Christina!
Would you like to come over?
Is this...
Yes, it's my home. It's really nice.
And what I like most about it...
is this bed!
Your bed?
It's really comfy! It actually
helps me have sweet dreams.
Huh... So that's what a
bed for lamia looks like.
It's amazing.
Sleep on it, and I bet you'll
be feeling warm and fuzzy, too!
Come!
Celina, it may be great for lamia,
but that may not necessarily
be the same for humans.
Sorry...
How is it?
It's very comfortable, yes.
Right?
It was Balan's idea!
Captain Balan?
As a lamia, I was honestly worried if
the villagers here would accept me.
But the more I get to know this village,
the more I love the people here.
Did you know? Balan loves
the milk his wife produces,
and he and the villagers compete over
who can drink the most in one sitting.
That explains why everyone
headed to his house earlier.
Dolan's older brother is a skilled fisher.
He's fished a sharke this big
out of the river once before.
I didn't know that river
even had fish of that size.
The other villagers have
their lovable quirks, too.
Malida is a soldier on the outside,
but she loves her sweets.
And Albert...
Dolan...
Why are you standing over there?
Huh? Oh...
Yes, why? You should join us on the bed.
No, I'll pass.
Well? Do you like it?
Yeah, it's great. Thanks as always.
You got that right!
Who's gonna step up and drink more
of my wife's milk than I can?
Will it be you? Or you?
Uh, maybe not today.
This is the place, Christina.
Oh, if it ain't Christina!
Please, join us here.
Thank you.
What brings you here today?
I thought I'd try some of the
milk you're so proud of.
Such a lovely thought.
I'll bring some right away.
It's as delicious as they say.
Very glad to hear it!
Could it be that you're quite the drinker?
I can certainly drink more than most.
Care to see if that includes me?
Don't blame me if I empty out
the village's milk supplies.
Cheers!
More!
Whoa. Captain Balan's our champion,
and he's having trouble keeping up.
Are you okay? You're not forcing yourself?
I could go for some more, if anything.
Um, Christina?
Could you taste something for me?
Wait, is that Mir's...
Yep.
I was hoping to have my
husband try it first,
but look at him now.
So if you could, Christina...
It's great.
It's sweet and goes down smoothly.
Could I have another jug?
Thank you!
Thanks to Dolan and Celina,
I got to grow closer to the villagers.
"Verun Village is starting to become
a place that's dear to my heart."
I see.
Wow, she's friends with a lamia?
That's our Christina, all right.
Oh? Please come in.
Have you heard?
It seems a student of the Magic Academy
has grown friendly with a lamia.
A lamia?!
Can humans and monsters even be friends?
It's Christina, yes?
Her exploits are the talk
of the town in Galoa.
They say that lamia is young and no
less beautiful than Christina herself.
Word sure gets around quickly, huh?
Could you tell me more about this lamia?
Keiren?
Why do you care about a mere lamia?
You're a mage employed by
the government-general.
Why wouldn't I?
Even alone, we mustn't discount
the threat it poses.
Humans aren't meant to live with
monsters as dangerous as lamia.
We have yet to resolve the recent
string of disappearances, too.
We have enough bad news.
I don't want any more.
While those incidents are
cause for concern...
The lamia is said to be gentle and kind,
and an oracle from Goddess Myrale told
people to live together with her.
Still, we must be prepared for the worst.
She should be summoned to Galoa at once.
Whose jurisdiction does
Verun Village fall under?
That would be me.
We must make the first move here.
I'll send an envoy at once.
I'm done, Dolan!
You've certainly planted them with care,
but you should probably
space them out more evenly.
As for Christina...
Well, that's an impactful sight.
Was that a tad too much force?
Dolan! And you too, Celina!
Cleth? What's the matter?
Come to the village gates at once!
Elder, what's going on here?
This way, Christina.
All hands, get in position!
I'm Gouda, Commissioner
of the Northern Frontier.
Would you be Dolan?
Yes.
I hear you brought the lamia into this
holy land given to you by our king.
Is this true?
Yes, that is correct.
Commissioner Gouda, must I repeat myself?
Our Goddess Myrale's oracle has already
proven that she isn't an evil monster.
Priestess Paramys, I'm not saying I doubt
our great goddess Myrale's judgment.
But I am responsible for these lands.
I must eliminate any threats
to it surely and swiftly.
I was afraid they'd sent a lamia-elimination
squad, but apparently not.
What are they after?
We'll take the lamia to the government-general
to confirm that she is truly safe.
Why do that if you do not
doubt the goddess's judgment?
Whatever the goddess may say,
if she is to live in Verun Village,
she must complete the procedures
Kingdom law deems necessary.
Such are the laws of our society.
Surely even you can understand, lamia.
Right...
Commissioner, I'm the one
who brought Celina in.
Therefore I would like to accompany her.
May I have your permission to do so?
Very well.
After all, we can't have her
acting out along the way.
That would force us to take
the necessary measures.
I'm worried about those two.
I should go ahead and talk to
the headmistress about this.
She has considerable influence
with the government-general.
Hear me, the laws of wind.
Give me the means to traverse your path.
Sylphied Boost!
This must be your first time
riding a carriage for so long.
Do you feel any pain?
I'm fine.
Aren't you cold?
I brought my blanket, so you can share it.
Allow me, then.
Special case, okay?
Don't worry, Celina. You'll be fine.
The procedures won't take long.
I'm more worried about the
trouble I caused everyone.
Because of me, even you had to...
Celina.
I'm taking a page out of my mother's book.
Whenever I was anxious, she would
pull me in and comfort me.
It'll be okay.
Don't worry about a thing.
If you feel bad about being a lamia,
then I'll have to give a talking-to
that lasts all night.
What?!
Excuse me, Headmistress!
I would like to discuss the commissioner's
visit to Verun Village.
That tells me all I need to know.
Take a seat first. I'll make some tea.
First things first.
Celina will not be eliminated.
She has Goddess Myrale's blessing.
Then why was she taken away?
It wasn't Commissioner Gouda
who decided to bring her here.
It was someone higher up the
ladder—the mage, Keiren.
Higher than the commissioner?
So, part of the government-general?
Keiren sees her as a threat,
and that she may be involved
in the recent disappearances.
Celina would never...
Of course not. It'd be impossible
for her, living out in Verun.
But if Keiren says so,
suspicion may very well fall on her.
What?!
Up. Commissioner Gouda has called for you.
Next Episode
This week's lucky item are cushions!
Look forward to next time!